Fixed Synced by bozxphd . Enjoy The Flick
[ LEAVES RUSTLING ]
[ WIND HOWLING ]
[ WIND GUSTING ]
[ LEAVES RUSTLING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
[ SIREN BLARING IN DISTANCE ]
[ INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER ]
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
It 's getting late , Officer .
[ INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER ]
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
Sheriff , you gotta get down here .
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
[ INTENSE MUSIC ]
We got an ID on her ?
No , Sir .
No relation to Paul and Carol .
Who 's she ?
Well , for now , she 's a Jane Doe .
You got something ?
Nothing was stolen .
Not a scratch on the outside of the house either .
Doesn 't look like someone broke in .
To me , it looks like they were trying to break out .
[ INTENSE MUSIC ]
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
[ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ]
[ SWITCH CLICKS ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ]
[ BUZZING ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ ROCK MUSIC ON STEREO ]
" I hit the floor around 4 : 47 with the mornin ' blues "
" Cryin ' like a puppy dog "
" It takes some time to come out "
" Face the music gotta pay your dues "
" You 're the only one I want "
" Best time tonight then I 'm gonna cry "
" Gotta put this right "
" I 've been dyin ' "
" Girl I just ain 't been feelin ' right "
" Yes I 'm in trouble I know it "
" You shot me down burning ' like a heart attack "
" All over you yeah "
" My brown-eyed girl "
" I guess I swear her hair was "
" I guess I swear her hair was midnight black "
" Midnight black Oh yeah "
" Midnight black Oh yeah " "
Cause of death ?
How about we skip this part tonight ?
Come on , this one 's a soft ball .
Smoke inhalation .
You 're telling me that smoke killed Mr. Howard ?
Well , damaged nasal passage
damaged throat , damaged lungs ..
Damaged lungs , yes .
But incompatible with life .
So , you 're saying that 's not the COD ?
I 'm saying look before you leap .
Where did the Police find the body ?
Uh , in his kitchen .
House on fire . Front door is 30 feet away
Yet , he 's not trying to get there .
Lungs are damaged
but airways not denuded nearly enough .
So , he stopped breathing
before that fire really got going ?
Open him up .
Now .
Now you see here ?
Down below the occipital . A fracture .
That explains the swelling in his brain .
Subdural hematoma .
That 's what did it . Not the smoke .
[ METAL CLANKS ]
Everybody has a secret .
Some just hide them better than others .
Some people are better at finding them .
You did good . You 'll get there .
Nobody 's even claimed him yet .
He was all alone , that 's why he died .
He died because he fell and hit his head .
[ CELL PHONE DINGS ]
You got plans tonight ?
Emma wants to go see a movie at The Strand .
I thought they 'd closed that place down .
Uh , no , when was the last time
you even went to go see a movie , Dad ?
Uh , she has Alzheimer 's
and he 's building her a house .
The Notebook ?
Oh , yeah , your mother made me go and see it with her
for her birthday .
I fell asleep five minutes in .
Yeah .
Are you alright finishing up ?
What 's up , Tilden ?
Hematoma .
[ GLASS CLINKS ]
[ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ RUMBLING ]
[ MEOWING ]
Stanley .
Oh .
Hey , Dad !
Stanley got another one .
[ THUDDING ]
Dad ?
[ BUZZING ]
[ SWITCH CLICKS ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ LAUGHING ]
Jesus Christ !
It 's so easy !
How 'd you get down here ?
The key was in the elevator .
Oh , my God .
I gotta say , this is not what I was expecting .
You said it was old but wow .
I thought we were supposed to meet out front .
Well , I got tired of waiting .
Where , where are you going ?
I 'm having a little look .
Come back .
God , the place just keeps going .
Well , three generations of Tildens keep expanding
end up with this state-of-the-art facility .
Hey , come on .
What 's the rush ?
I 've been down here all day .
You got to see me at my job , why can 't I see you at yours ?
You work at a book store .
Are these all people ?
Just three tonight .
Can I see one ?
Well , no . No . You cannot see one .
Why not ?
Because there 's ...
Some things you can 't un-see , okay ?
Come on , I can handle it .
No . No . And my dad is way too strict .
Try me .
So , what 'll it be ?
Are you serious ?
Are you ?
Hell yeah .
Pick one .
Not that one .
The one next to it .
A body 's a body .
Yeah , well , I pick that one .
[ METAL CREAKS ]
[ BELL RINGING ]
[ INTENSE MUSIC ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
What 's that for ?
To make sure he 's dead .
There used to be a time it was hard to tell
a comatose person from a dead one .
So coroners tied bells to everybody in the morgue .
So if they heard a ' ting
they knew somebody down there
wasn 't quite ready to go .
So , why do you have one ?
Well , I 'm ... I 'm a bit of a traditionalist .
Why did you cover his face ?
There wasn 't much of a face left to cover .
Point blank gun shot blast tend to do that .
Who shot him ?
Angle of entry suggests he did it to himself .
until we found Strychnine in his system
And judging by the progress it made through his bloodstream
he was already dead by the time somebody blew his face off .
Why would anyone do that ?
You sound like your boyfriend .
Leave the " why " to the cops and the shrinks .
We 're just here to find cause of death .
No more , no less .
You don 't wanna see that .
It 's alright .
[ BELL RINGING ]
[ LAUGHS ]
[ METAL RATTLING ]
Look who 's easy now .
You should have seen the look on your face .
I can 't wait to see the look on your face
when you 're not getting laid tonight .
Whoa , whoa . Hold on . Hold on . Hold on .
Not even if I ply you with popcorn and sourpatch kids ?
You 're lucky you 're cute .
How do you get used to that ?
You do and you don 't .
[ ELEVATOR DINGS ]
Sheriff ?
Where 's your dad ? What happened ?
Bring her back here , Sheldon .
Dad , if you need me to stay ...
Oh , don 't worry about it .
You two go have your fun .
Did you see the look on Burke 's face ?
I mean , he wouldn 't be here this late if it wasn 't important .
Here we go .
Well , my dad ... There it is .
I can 't ditch him .
So you 're ditching me again .
What 's he gonna do when you leave ?
You haven 't told him yet ?
No . It 's not that simple .
Wow .
Babe .
I 'm gonna tell him , okay ?
Hey , you think I wanna be here ?
Down there ?
This isn 't my life .
I don 't wanna be Austin Tilden , the morgue worker .
Just , he needs my help right now .
Come on , it 's been two years .
He can take care of himself .
Come back in a few hours .
We 'll catch the midnight show , grab a drink at Thornton 's ..
Two drinks .
11 o 'clock , I 'm all yours . I promise .
And don 't , you know , don 't smile
because a smile means " yes " you know .
I know it 's in there .
Now , you 're gonna blow your whole game .
Maybe .
You 're hot !
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
[ INTENSE MUSIC ]
[ ZIPPER UNZIPS ]
Found her in the basement of the Douglas ' place .
No ID , no fingerprints in the system .
No one has a clue who she is .
I don 't suppose you know how she wound up there ?
[ CAT GROWLING ]
Stanley .
Damn thing gets meaner by the day .
Alvarez there was working at Paul and Carol 's place .
My best bet ? He killed our Jane Doe .
Needed a place to dump the body .
Didn 't count the Douglas' being home
or Paul having a.38.
First thing tomorrow , I 'll bring him in
but for now , she 's the priority .
Oh , still , it would have been nice
to take a look at the crime scene
I got four people dead
and no god damn clue how any of it connects .
Nobody 's pissin in your grits here , Shel .
But we do have protocol .
Press is gonna need answers on this in the morning
and I got nothing .
Now they 'll buy a 10-79 .
I can give them a B and E gone haywire .
But what I can 't sell is her .
Time frame ?
It 's gotta be tonight .
Okay .
You didn 't have to come back .
I know .
[ SHUTTER COLLAPSES ]
[ ROCK MUSIC ]
[ ZIPPER UNZIPS ]
[ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ]
This is the autopsy of an unidentified female
henceforth known as " Jane Doe . "
Performing the autopsy will be myself
Tommy Tilden , attending coroner .
I will be assisted by Austin Tilden
certified medical technician .
This autopsy will be conducted in four stages
beginning with an external evaluation
followed by an internal evaluation
of the heart and lungs , the digestive organs
and finally , the brain .
We 've got some beautiful weather here
for the next few days .
Subject is in her mid to late 20s .
Appears to be .
Subject appears to be in her mid to late 20s .
Caucasian . Skin appears normal .
No outwards signs of bleeding or bruising .
No scarring , no distinctive external markings .
[ CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS ]
Hair , brown .
Eyes ..
grey ?
Huh .
You don 't see clouding like that
unless a body 's been dead for days .
There 's no lividity .
No rigor mortis either .
When do you think she died ?
Well , she 's colder than the ambient temperature .
What , conditions at the scene ?
Could be confounding factors .
Look how small her waist is .
Like it doesn 't really fit the rest of her frame .
Could be congenital .
We won 't know until we open her up .
Mark it down on the board . We 'll come back to it later .
[ BONES CRACKING ]
Her wrists and ankles are fractured .
How do you break your wrists and ankles
without any outward signs ?
Oh , I see it all the time .
Simple fractures .
Simple ? Uh-uh . Her joints are shattered .
What is that ? What is it ? Dirt ?
No , no , this is denser .
Heavier .
It 's ... This is peat .
Haven 't seen this stuff in ages .
It 's under her toenails , too .
Yeah . There are trace amounts in the hair .
She 's covered in it .
Like , maybe she was buried in it ?
Where do you even find peat ?
But naturally in the ground ..
up north .
Not around here .
Nasal passages , no sign of inflammation .
No fluid and no foreign substances
and ear canals are ..
clear .
Oh .
I hadn 't expected that .
Tongue has been ...
Severed .
Crudely . Non surgically .
Well , she could have bitten it off , you know
she ODs on something , tensed up ...
These aren 't bite marks .
I 've seen something like this before
about 15 years back .
Human trafficking around Norfolk .
Two girls
hands and feet
bound tight
to keep them from running .
Cut out their tongues
for making too much noise ...
You think this was some kind of a prostitution thing ?
Can 't rule it out .
[ EERIE MUSIC ]
[ FLY BUZZING ]
[ ZAPS ]
[ CAMERA HERE CLICKS ]
Here , she has a molar missing on the lower left side .
Take some impressions .
It 's definitely some kind of fabric .
Bag it . Send it to the lab .
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
[ CLATTERS ]
No external seminal fluid present .
Give me a swab .
[ SIGHS ]
Ah , she 's torn up inside .
There are ridges , grooves in the tissue .
Abrasions ?
No . Cuts .
Deliberate .
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
Severed tongue , shattered joints
vaginal trauma ..
The theory tracks .
We got a ways to go .
We 'll now proceed with the internal examination
starting with the heart and lungs .
Help me with the block .
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
[ ELECTRICAL CRACKLING ]
[ INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER ]
" Let the sun shine in "
" Mommy told me something "
" A little girl should know "
" It 's all about the devil "
[ UPBEAT MUSIC ON RADIO ]
[ EERIE MUSIC ]
They 're not supposed to bleed like that . Right ?
I 've seen it .
An hour dead , maybe two .
It 's caused by a build up of pressure .
What is that ?
Melanoma maybe ?
On the inside ?
Possible .
Let 's see what the lab comes back with .
Can you hand me the rib cutters ?
[ DRIPPING ]
Today ?
Shit .
What did you do ?
Oh , I got it .
I need you to focus here .
I got it .
Well , you were right .
Her waist doesn 't fit her frame .
It 's not congenital .
Then what is it ?
Well , if you wear one long enough , a corset ...
Didn 't those go out of style a couple of hundred years ago ?
[ RIB BONES CRACKING ]
The lungs
severely blackened .
Wouldn 't have taken her for a smoker .
ten packs a day for 30 years
wouldn 't explain this .
But that 's what killed her , right ?
I 'd expect the body to be covered in third degree burns .
It 's like finding a ... a bullet in the brain
but with no gunshot wound .
Her heart 's marked up .
Almost like it 's been cut .
Well , not just her heart .
What do you think that is ? Genetic defect ?
Scar tissue ?
From what ?
Imagine all this internal trauma
was reflected externally .
Shattered ankles and wrists
fire-burned lungs , scarred organs .
What would she look like ?
She 'd be mangled .
Disfigured beyond recognition
but she 's not .
I mean , how the hell do you even do this ?
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
[ CRACKLING ]
If you wanna kill someone you shoot them
A million easy ways .
You don 't go to these lengths
unless you wanna make them suffer
[ BANGING ON DOOR ]
What the ...
I 'll get it .
You buy it at a nursery .
So clean .
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
[ EERIE MUSIC ]
See , striations . Huh ?
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
What happened to you ?
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
[ CRACKS ]
[ GROANS ]
[ SWITCH CLICKS ]
[ RATTLING ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC ]
[ CRASHING ]
[ SWITCH CLICKS ]
What the hell happened ?
Are you okay ?
Something 's in the vent .
[ GRUNTS ]
Thanks .
Oh , shit .
[ STANLEY WHIMPERS ]
[ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ]
[ BONES SNAPS ]
We 're barely out of the external .
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
[ SWITCH CLICKS ]
[ INCINERATOR RUMBLES ]
Give me a minute .
What are you doing ?
The drawer ..
Must have not closed it all the way .
[ SIGHS ]
[ INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO ]
Stanley was a pain in the ass .
But he was your mother 's .
One of the few things of hers I had left .
Yeah , I miss her , too .
Right . Let 's keep going .
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
But only on a fresh corpse .
and the gastro-intestinal system .
Dad , you can talk to me .
I 'm not keeping anything from you .
You just ... you put up this act for people ...
I 'm fine .
Alright .
What is that ?
A flower ?
[ CLATTERS ]
[ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ]
Probably explains the inflammation on her organs .
Hmm . Here 's a weird thing .
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
That settles it . She 's from up north .
Yeah , but how did she end up here ?
One thing at a time .
I 'm just trying to make sense of all this .
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
Gusts are now being reported at up to 60 miles per hour .
Rain is expected to top three inches within the hour .
This one might be a bigger deal than we were led to believe .
Dad , how about we just finish this in the morning ?
She could smoke
When we start something , we finish it .
No , this amount of lung damage though
It looks like some kind of shroud .
Probably scar tissue .
I mean , the fact that it 's intact at all is amazing .
Now see , what is that ?
Okay .
These numerals .
The order . T and ... and this S.
or poison them or drown them .
What are you doing ?
Someone pulled out her tooth
wrapped it in fabric and forced her
And the drawing ?
I don 't know . Religious ?
Possibly , uh , ritualistic ?
Well , let 's play that one out .
Every ritual has its purpose .
What MO have we seen so far ?
Then they ripped out her tongue , poisoned her
paralyzed her forced her to swallow the cloth .
Then , uh , the cuts , the internal mutilation , stabs .
Then as if that wasn 't enough , they burned her .
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
Almost like a human sacrifice
I got to tell you we have serious weather reports
coming in from all the monitoring stations across the state .
We 've got a flash flood warning now in full effect
for all of Grantham County .
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
They 've got concerns about ..
You can 't kill someone this way
without leaving a trace on the outside .
She doesn 't even have a broken nail .
If we could just find out why she was tortured ...
Down here , if you can 't see it
touch it , it doesn 't matter .
Now , these bodies are not just CODs , dad .
This happened to her for a reason .
Trust me when I tell you
this is not a storm you wanna get caught in , folks .
If you 're home , stay home .
One thing 's for sure .
You 're not going anywhere .
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
" Mommy told me something "
" A little girl should know "
" It 's all about the devil "
" And I 've learned to hate him so "
Hey , dad ?
" She say he causes trouble when .. "
I think maybe we should get out of here .
" He will never ever leave you "
" If your heart if filled with gloom "
" So let the sun shine in "
" Face it with a grin "
" Smilers never lose .. "
Help me with this .
" So let the sun shine in "
" Open up your heart and let the sun shine in "
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
Holy shit .
" When the light comes pouring in "
" I 'm happy because I never wear a frown "
[ CREAKING ]
" So let the sun shine in "
[ ELECTRICAL CRACKLING ]
[ THUDDING ]
[ PANTING ]
What the fuck ?
Dad ? ⌧ ⌧ Dad ?
Here !
[ INTENSE MUSIC ]
Let 's get the fuck out of here .
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
Come on , come on .
The generator .
There 's not enough power .
[ THUDDING ]
[ THUNDER RUMBLING ]
It 's stuck .
Help me with this . Help me with this !
[ GRUNTING ]
The old sycamore fell .
[ WHIRRING ]
[ PANTING ]
Fuck !
The office . The landline .
[ THUMPING ]
What the hell was that ? I don 't know .
[ DIAL TONE BUZZING ]
Oh , thank God .
Harding County Sheriff Department .
This is Tommy Tilden . It 's an emergency . We need help .
Sorry , I 've trouble hearing ...
Put Burke on the line .
This is Burke .
Sheldon , this is Tommy . You better get over here now .
Hello ? Tommy , I can scarcely hear you . Your voice is breaking up .
Sheldon ! Sheldon , we 're trapped down here , godda ..
Sheldon , please ... Tommy .
[ BELL JINGLING ]
Beginning with the stomach
[ BELL JINGLING CONTINUES ]
Jimson weed . Paralyzing agent .
[ INTENSE MUSIC ]
[ BANGING ON DOOR ]
What the fuck is going on ?
It 's her .
Everything was fine until Burke wheeled her through that door .
Burke needs a COD tonight .
We 're not even close .
You wanna leave ..
leave .
These things we found inside her
her injuries , those marks .
You can 't say she 's just a body .
[ GRUNTING ]
We should have left .
I wanted to leave .
Dad !
Oh .
No !
Dad ! Dad !
Roman numerals ?
[ THUDDING ]
Hmm . And old .
Stomach acids should have dissolved this thing .
[ GRUNTING ]
Oh , my God .
Careful , careful .
[ GROANING ]
Oh , God ! Ohh .
Help me up . Yeah .
I 'm fine .
They were grey .
Her eyes .
It had her eyes .
That 's what I 've been trying to tell you .
It 's her .
Oh , no , that 's not possible .
It doesn 't fit .
to swallow it .
we are way past possible .
It 's her .
First they bound her .
[ INTENSE MUSIC ]
Rapid decomp .
Everything we took out of her .
That 's almost like her body was preserving it .
Must get her to the crematorium .
[ AUSTIN GASPS ]
[ RATTLING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
" Face it with a grin "
[ INTENSE MUSIC ]
[ SCREAMING ]
Fuck it .
Jesus !
Behind you , the extinguisher .
The pin . Pull the pin .
No .
[ ELEVATOR RUMBLES ]
The elevator .
[ ELEVATOR DINGS ]
Come on .
No , no , no , no ! Fuck !
[ BELL RINGING ]
Come on . Come on . Come on .
[ BELL RINGING CONTINUES ]
Come on !
[ ELEVATOR DINGS ]
[ BELL RINGING CONTINUES ]
Go , dad . Come on .
This is stage three of the autopsy of Jane Doe .
Come on .
[ BELL RINGING CONTINUES ]
[ GROANING ]
Emma .
Oh , no !
Oh , no , no !
Oh , my God !
Oh , no ! No !
No !
Oh , my God .
Oh , no , no , no ! Austin ..
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC ]
[ ELEVATOR DINGS ]
Son ... Until we cut into her .
You 're talking about a corpse .
Come on , son .
[ ELEVATOR RATTLING ]
Fuck !
[ GRUNTING ]
I told her to come back for me .
I told her to come back .
No , you didn 't do this .
You shouldn 't be here .
All this is my fault .
You couldn 't have known . Yeah .
Yeah , that 's what everyone told me ..
about your mom .
Dad ?
Oh , shit . Oh ..
Ray of sunshine .
She thought it was corny as shit .
[ CHUCKLES ]
But it stuck .
If I 'd have known , I would have helped her .
You know that , don 't you ?
I mean , she was always so bright .
So happy .
[ CREAKING ]
I should 've seen it .
But I didn 't .
She had to deal with it alone .
All these mistakes ..
my mistakes ..
and you had to pay for them .
Whatever the hell happened in here ..
So , what do we do ?
No , her body
those things we found inside , those were impossible .
[ RUMBLING ]
Why hasn 't she killed us yet ?
Well , it 's not for want of trying .
Well , look what she can do ..
if she wanted us dead .
When we cut into her ..
she tried to stop us each time .
It 's like there 's something she doesn 't want us to find .
You wanna go back in there ?
If we stay here , we 're dead .
If we could just figure out how she died ..
maybe we can figure out how to stop her .
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC ]
[ COUGHING ]
Dad ? Right behind you .
Keep moving .
Austin ?
[ SCREECHING ]
Ah ! Dad ?
No !
Dad ?
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GROANING ]
Dad . Dad .
Come on . Come on .
Come on .
Okay .
[ WHIRRING ]
Brain ... is normal .
There 's got to be something .
All her other organs are scarred .
[ INTENSE MUSIC ]
What the fuck ?
What is it ?
That 's why we couldn 't find cause of death .
She 's still alive .
Alive ?
We should lit her on fire .
We took out her heart .
There 's something , some energy .
Call it what you want , something is keeping her going .
What the ..
Leviticus .
Let me see that .
Twenty . Twenty seven .
If these are Roman numerals
then they 'd be ..
1693 .
" Any man or woman
" who consults the spirits of the dead
" shall be put to death
for they are .. "
Dad .
Seventeenth century .
New England .
" They are a witch
and their blood shall be on their own heads . "
It fits .
Austin , the elevator .
Come on , now . Come on .
There were no witches in Salem .
They were kids . Young girls .
Falsely accused , wrapped up in hysteria
One pointing to the next , who pointed to the next
But they were all , all innocent .
Only ... they didn 't hang her ..
or burn her at the stake .
They tortured her ..
mercilessly .
The ritual .
It didn 't work .
What if ..
What if
the ritual , performed on an innocent
accidentally created the very thing we 're trying to destroy ?
Everything they did to her .
Everything we 've done to her .
She can feel it .
She wants us ... to feel it too .
You know why I used to call her Ray ?
That 's why she 's keeping us alive .
This is her revenge .
This is her ritual .
But why us ?
Why the Douglas ' ?
Why anybody ?
We 're on her path , that 's all .
We were just stops along the way .
Those who survived got rid of her
and buried her as far away as possible .
That hasn 't stopped her .
Because no one got close enough .
To think she was carrying around all that
pain , all that unhappiness every day .
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC ]
and it won 't stop .
It won 't stop until ..
Until what ?
Dad , until what ?
I won 't fight you .
But please ..
please don 't hurt him .
Let me help you .
Dad !
Dad ?
[ GRUNTING ]
No !
Dad !
[ GRUNTING ]
Dad .
No .
Please ..
[ SCREAMING ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC ]
[ SOBBING ]
Tommy !
Austin ! Are you there ?
Burke ?
Anyone there ?
Burke .
Austin !
Austin ! Are you down there ?
We 're sawing down a tree blocking your door .
We 'll be with you right now , alright .
Austin !
I 'm here !
You 'll be alright .
Just open up the door now .
It 's stuck . Try again , son .
I can 't . It won 't .
Should open up now .
It won 't . Should open up .
I 'm trying . It 's stuck .
Open up .
I can 't . Open up !
I can 't .
" Open up your heart "
" And let the sun shine in "
" So let the sun shine in "
" Face it with a grin "
" Smilers never lose "
" Frowners never win "
" So let the sun shine in " "
[ SCREAMING ]
[ INTENSE MUSIC ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER RADIO ]
No obvious signs of forced entry .
Looks an awful lot like he ...
I 've known his family
Whatever it looks like , that ain 't it .
Well , it 's going to be another nice one out there .
Today 's our fourth straight day of sunshine .
Looking at a high of 75 .
Beautiful outdoor weather
but remember to use your sunscreen .
What the hell happened here ?
What do you want to do with her ?
Get her out of here . Already got a car waiting .
There 's that , uh , funeral home over in Ruxton .
Get her out of my county .
Take her over to VCU .
Let Ward Lamon deal with her .
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC ]
North East .
Witches are a myth .
You can 't keep denying .
Now , baby , listen that was one time .
Hell , yes , that 's a promise .
" The word of God is powerful . "
" Open up your heart and let the sun shine in "
" So let the sun shine in "
" Smilers never lose and frowners never win "
" Face it with a grin "
" Open up your heart and let the sun shine in " "
[ BELL JINGLES ]
[ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
She 's still suffering ..
No one could see what we have seen .